Trick them and snatch it!
Kaiji returns to the silver screen!
And we give you loyal anime watchers a sneak peek!
I'll win. For sure.
Kaiji's actor, Tatsuya Fujiwara, appears in the next episode of the anime!
This is awkward.
There's so many people around.
He'll play that tender man in black comics fans know so well!
Who? Who?!?
Go ahead.
Stand up, please.
Come on.
Perfect. You nailed it in one.
Thanks!
Keep your eyes peeled for the scene he nailed, next episode!
Seeing that scene again will be shocking.
I hope you all enjoy it.
Tatsuya Fujiwara stars in Kaiji 2: Jinsei Dakkai Game, this November 5th!
The ultimate barrier rises from nowhere to bar Kaiji!
突如 カイジの前に立ちふさがった
究極の壁　｢風のカーテン｣
A curtain of wind!
Kaiji is defeated!
カイジ 敗北
Bitter Tears
くっ　カイジ…
Kaiji!
Out of the way.
ほら　降りろ
触るな　待て
Fuck off!
Wait! Just hold it!
いいから待て！
I've still got money!
金はまだあるんだ
I still have the 800 thou I came up with with!
地下を出る時 受け取った80万が
I spent a little bit, but there's still 720 left!
ちょっと使っちまったが 72万
This... I can keep playing with this!
これでまだ打てるはず　これで…
What the hell are you doing!?
何しやがる！
ハハハ…
No. No, you can't. Not with pocket change like that.
ダメダメ　打てません
そんな はした金では
If you want to buy Paqy for the Bog, you've got to cough up at least three mil.
沼のパッキーは最低300万
そ… そこを何とか　バラ売りで
Come on! Just sell me one!
I'm afraid not.
Now, if you'll kindly be on your way?
お引き取りを
Ichijou!
一条！
ほら　降りろ
Somebody help me!
誰か 助けろ！金を…
Money! Just lend me a little money!
金を貸せ！
俺に あと少し
I almost got it!
あと少しなんだ
Just a little bit more, and I'll have it beat!
もう少しで攻略なんだ！
You can see that, can't you!?
分かるだろ？
誰でも… 誰でもいいから
Anything! Anyone!
Just lend me some money!
貸せ　つぎ込め 俺に！
Invest in me!
Give me another chance to play!
俺で勝負しろ
誰か 俺で勝負しろ！
Somebody! Take a chance!
カイジさん　カイジさん
Kaiji...
Kaiji!
It's over.
終わっちまった
イヒ　イヒ　イヒ　イヒ
イヒハハハ…
誰か！俺で勝負を　勝負を…
Somebody take a chance on me!
A chance!
てやっ
バカが！
You fool.
あり得ないんだよ そんなこと
There's no way that's going to happen.
誰が貸すか
Who the hell would lend you money after a performance like that?
敗者
負け犬に！
To a loser like you?
負けたんだよ お前は！
You've lost!
You're trash!
クズ　破産　破産だ
Broke!
破産！
You're broke!
誰だ？
Who's there?
Ichijou.
一条はん
You're a terrible person.
あんたは ひどい人や
この声…
何？
That voice is...
What?
—The last penny a man has...
実際 なけなしの金
最後の金っちゅうもんは
あれ？
この声…
—Huh?
This voice...?
Is his last glimmer of hope.
その人間にとって
まさに命のともしび
生きる希望そのもの
The only hope left in his life!
And you use this monster to steal it away!
それをあんたは奪ってきたんや
この怪物で無慈悲に！
It's the rules of the game. Fair's fair.
勝負の結果だ　正当な…
正当やない！
No, it's not!
You could flip this thing over, and not one ball would come rolling out!
こいつは逆さに降っても
玉１つ こぼれん
It really is the devil's own machine!
そういう悪魔の台
And you know this better than anyone!
あんたが一番よく知っとるはずや
Dozens of men...
何十人
No, their families too!
いや その家族
縁者を入れれば
The Man-Eating Bog must have devoured the hopes, the very lives, of over a hundred people!
100に届こうっちゅう人間が
この人食い沼によって
最後の望みを絶たれ
死んでいった
自ら… 自ら！
By their own hands! Their own hands!
し… 知るか そんな話！
I don't care about that!
Each and every one of these silver balls gathered here...
ここに たまっている
銀玉その１つ１つが
Is a tear! A tear formed from their regret and resentment!
まるで涙…
散っていった人間たちの
悔恨　怨嗟の涙
その結晶！
It's a deadly sin.
罪深い話や　つくづく…
Oh so deadly.
万死に値する！
And you'll burn for it!
カイジ！
Kaiji!
We're not just playing for ourselves here.
この勝負は
わしらだけのもんじゃない
We're playing for everyone who's lost it all to the Bog!
この沼によって散っていった
数多の破産者
We're fighting to give their souls rest!
その人間たちの無念を
晴らす戦いや
We have to avenge them!
勝たにゃならん！
何としても勝つんや！
We have to win no matter what!
That's why I brought the rest of that money.
そのために持ってきて
さっき放った金が1000万
Ten million.
And another ten million here!
さらに ここに1000万や！
Twenty million all together.
都合2000万を
Kaiji!
カイジ！この金で打て 敵を！
Take this money, and take our vengeance!
Make that devil spit up every dirty cent it's swallowed!
この悪魔の不当な蓄え　収奪金を
全部 吐き出させろ！
おっちゃん　おっちゃん
Pops...
おっちゃん！
なに いつまで待ってんだ
Are you done yet!?
Let me go!
放せ　金は… 金ならここにある
If it's money you want, here it is!
You've got nothing to complain about now, Ichijou!
文句はねえだろ　一条！
Right, Ichijou!?
そうだろ　一条！
カイジ！
Kaiji!
Endoh!
遠藤さん
カイジ！
Kaiji!
Pops...
おっちゃん
起死回生のファインプレーだ
If you didn't cover me there, I'd be dead meat.
この金… 例のあれだな
You went back to the well, huh?
You got it.
正解　社長は出張
The boss was out of town.
おまけに今日は日曜で会社は休み
ツイとった
It's Sunday, so there's no one else around.
So I just took it.
You really are something.
何をいけしゃあしゃあと
１度ならず２度までも
ひどいガードマンだぜ
Going back for more?
You're a terrible guard.
What're you talking about? I'm just borrowing it.
何を言う　ちょっと借りただけ
返せば何の問題もない
All I have to do is bring it back, and no one will even notice.
Can't argue with that.
…ったく　そのとおりだ
A miraculous turnaround!
まさに起死回生　土壇場のカイジ
Kaiji, on the gallows!
Here...
ど… どうぞ
地獄の淵からの生還！
He returns alive from the bowels of hell!
まったく そのとおりだ
He's absolutely right.
Kaiji!
カイジさん！
そうだ　まだ終わってねえ
That's right! It's not over yet!
Go for it!
頑張れ！
あきらめるな！
Don't give up!
カイジさん！
いけ！
Go!
That's right.
そうだ　勝つこと
I have to win.
If I win, then everything's fine.
勝てば問題ない
勝てば すべて正しくなる
If I win, that solves everything.
きれいに解決する
I will win.
俺は勝つ
俺は… 勝つ！
I. Will. Win.
俺は勝つ！
I will win!
どんな不運　ツキのなさに
見舞われても
I don't care how unlucky I am! I don't care how I feel! I'll never give up!
決してあきらめない　ねじふせる
I'll turn everything around!
No matter if I'm doomed, no matter what's happening, no matter what's in my way...
最悪の運命　境遇
あらゆる障害　不平　不満
Even if I hate it! Even if I can't stand it!
I'll turn everything around and win in the end!
すべてをねじふせる
俺は勝つ！
当然だ
Of course!
俺は そのために生きている！
That's why I'm alive!
To win!
勝つ！
He wins to live!
生きるために勝つ
He lives to win!
勝つために生きる
The game resumes!
勝負 再開！
I'll make it through this.
乗り越える
I'll defend my own life.
俺の人生をふさぐ この絶望
Even as this despair closes in on me, chokes me, closes the path before me...
俺を押さえつけ 締めつけ
道を閉ざす
のしかかる障害
俺の未来を潰し
ふさごうとしているこの峰を
As this peak threatens to snuff out my future...
越える
I will overcome it!
いけ
Go!
The summit is right there!
頂はすぐそこ
Right in front of my eyes!
すぐ目の前
いけ！
Go!
Please, please, please!
頼む　頼む　頼む…
Look at that!
おい 見ろよ
何だよ これ
What's going on!?
す… すげえ！
Wow!
異様な光景
An unthinkable sight!
次々と３段目クルーンに
送り込まれる玉
Balls rolls into the third tray, one after the other!
They leave an unthinkable sight!
それが異様な光景を生む
埋め尽くす玉　玉　玉！
Balls, balls, balls! They bury the tray!
All right. You don't need to leap for me anymore.
よし　もう飛ぶまでもねえ
押せ　押してねじ込め！
Push! Shove it in!
押せ！
Push!
What's this? What the hell is going on?
何だ？
何なんだよ これは？
The guard of wind is as sure as one of steel!
風のガードは鉄板　鉄のガード
No matter how many balls there are, not one can get through.
銀玉など いくら来ても
はじき返せる
いわば砦からの機銃掃射
It's like machine gunfire raining down on infantrymen from a fortress!
要塞 対 歩兵
It should be a lock!
100パーセント勝てる勝負
But in in this kind of situation...
だが この異常事態！
膨大すぎる
It's too much!
They don't even die!
しかも こいつらは死なない
They're immortal soldiers!
死がふさがってる兵だ
It's ridiculous! It's nothing I ever could have predicted!
バカな　想定外　こんなこと
At this rate, it doesn't matter where the balls roll!
このままいけば
もう玉の軌道もクソもない
敷き詰めた玉が玉を押し
They'll spread out on the tray and push themselves straight in!
直接　直接…
無理だ！
It's impossible!
The wind can't hold that many back!
そんなもの
風なんかで押し返せるわけ…
分かった　カイジ
Fine!
Kaiji!
A draw! A draw!
引き分け… 引き分けだ
引き分けで手を打とう
Let's call it a draw!
生き残らせてやる
I'll let you live!
お前を特別に
遅い！
You're a day late and a dollar short, Ichijou.
もう… 遅い！
Kaiji!
カイジ
Please!
頼む！そこを… そこを何とか！
Come on! Please!
遅い！
You're too late!
離れろ　近づくな
Get away! Stay back!
カイジ！
離れろ
Kaiji!
Stay back!
カイジ！
Kaiji!
何や？
What's that sound?
台が鳴り出した
It's crying...
The Bog is crying!
沼が鳴き出しおった
What does this mean?
どういうこった こりゃあ？
カイジくん
Kaiji!
I don't know.
知らねえ
が 断末魔ってやつか？これが
Maybe it's its death rattle.
The dying scream of this demonic Bog!
この悪魔　沼の断末魔か
ヘヘヘ　どうした？
What's wrong? Does that hurt?
ずいぶんと苦しそうじゃねえか
この悪魔
You devil!
ド悪魔め！
You fucking devil!
Spit it out!
吐き出せ　そんなに出したきゃ
If you want to cry that much, then spit it out!
吐き出せ！
The lives of everyone that you devoured!
お前が食ってきた人間たちの
その命を！
Their hope, despair, all of it!
希望　絶望　そのすべてを！
Throw it up!
吐き出せ！
The time has come!
時 満ちる
The breaking point has been reached!
飽和状態
包み込まれた当たり穴
The jackpot hole is enveloped!
It's the critical moment!
臨界点！
Push! Push!
押せ　押せ　押せ　押せ…
やめろ　やめてくれ
Stop! Please, stop!
頼む　やめて
Please, stop, I'm begging you!
やめて　頼む
Push! Push it over!
押せ　押し殺せ！
Stop!
やめろ
やめろ　やめろ
Stop! Stop! Stop!!!
やめろー！
悪魔　終わりだ！
It's over, devil!
神さま
God...
Thank you!
ありがとう
ありがとうございます！
カ… カイジくん
Kaiji!
おい おい… 入ったよな？
Hey, hey!
It went in, right?
Yeah!
坂崎
遠藤はん！
Sakazaki...
Endoh!
It went in!
入った　入賞！
It got in!
The jackpot!
大当たり！
大当たりだ！
He hit the jackpot!
カイジ　カイジ　カイジ
カイジ　カイジ　カイジ…
Kaiji! Kaiji!
あっ　何や？
What's happening!?
光り出した　沼が！
It's shining!
The Bog is.. The Bog is—
沼が！
沼が光り出した！
The Bog is shining!
開く　すべての希望をはねつけ
It opens! All their hope, their struggle, their fears, their suffering!
抗い 飲み込み
固く… 固く閉ざされていた
悪魔の口が！
From the mouth of the demon, once clamped shut...
解放！
It all flows forth!
解放！解放！
It flows forth! It flows forth! It flows forth!!!
解放！
Awesome!
解放だ！
It's letting it all out!
至る所が…
All over!
開いてる　ガバガバ
It's opening up all over!
Everywhere!
There's so many!
すっげえ広いわ 台　入れ放題だ
It's like a playroom!
出る！出る！
Look at them all come out!
ひと玉 4000円がいくらでも！
Thousands of 4000-yen balls!
至福　パチンカーの夢
Pure bliss! A pachinko player's fantasy!
おっちゃん　ドル箱だ
ドル箱 持ってこい！
Pops! Go get the ball trays!
Get me some ball trays!
Sure thing!
おう　分かった
Ecstasy! Delight! Avaricious bliss!
恍惚　歓喜
垂涎の至福
喜々として働く坂崎
Sakazaki, a joyful laborer.
至福の雑用
Endoh only stands and watches!
遠藤　ただ突っ立っているだけ
A blissful observer!
至福の傍観
Kaiji shares their euphoria!
無論 カイジも至福
桃源郷をさまようがごとくの
圧倒的 至福
Overwhelming bliss, as if he trod Paradise for just one moment!
解放
They're released!
しかも狂喜乱舞
Underground, sheer revelry!
Ecstasy! Delight! Tears of gratitude! Weeping! Passion! Gratitude!
咆哮　歓喜　感涙
嗚咽　感動　感謝
圧倒的 感謝
Overwhelming gratitude!
この大当たりにより
カイジは なし得たのだ
With this, Kaiji has succeeded!
He has won the 45s the miracle of freedom!
４５組 奇跡の救出を！
Dad... You were right...
父さん…
父さんの言ったとおりだったね
Kaiji is...
カイジさんは… カイジさんは…
さんざ引っ張って
I can't tolerate this!
何じゃ この決着は！
How did you let this happen!?
胸くそ悪い
I'm disgusted.
クズが！
あんなゴミに足をすくわれおって
You were beaten by scum! Trash!
使えん　とことん使えん
Completely useless!
He makes me sick to my stomach!
ヘドが出るわ
There's no question about it.
こうなった以上 何の躊躇もない
地下行きだ！
He's going underground!
確か地下懲役の目安は… おい！
And what's the rate for underground labor?
You there!
あっ はい　ええと その
Yes! It's, er, fifteen years per ten million yen!
1000万で15年でございます
I see.
そうか　なら奴が帝愛に与えた
７億の損害は
Since he lost Teiai 700 million...
15 years by 70.
15年の70倍
1050年 地下行きだ！
1,050 years underground!
伝えろ すぐに！
はっ
Inform them immediately!
おい　いつまで
流しとるんだ こんなもの
Hey! How long are you going to keep broadcasting this?!
す… すみません　すぐに
I'm sorry, sir! I'll have it stopped right away!
I'm going to go sleep.
寝る
ハァーッ
Who just sighed?
今 ホッとした者
I...
あ… いえ…
制裁！
Deal with him.
Proverbs of Kaiji Returns!
A joyful laborer, a blissful observer.
Kaiji S2 DVD boxset 1 goes on sale September 21st.
The extras will leave you going "zawa zawa".
Reaching You finally hits Blu-ray September 21st!
The limited-edition boxset includes all eight discs!
KnT fans will love it!